http://www.eaglerocktradingpost.com/privacy-policy

*PRIVACY POLICY- EAGLE ROCK TRADING POST-Native American Jewelry
Native American Indian Jewelry | Turquoise Jewelry | Southwest Jewelry - EAGLE ROCK TRADING POST
*Golf Markers
*Spoons/Bowls/Etc.
Menu
YOUR place for Mens and Womens Vintage Native American Indian Jewelry, Southwest Turquoise Jewelry including Navajo, Hopi, Santo Domingo and Zuni
Jewelry, Pottery and Miscellaneous Native American Crafts.
*Golf Markers
*Spoons/Bowls/Etc.
My Account
Privacy PolicyInformation Collection & Use   Eagle Rock Trading Post is the sole owner of the information collected at Eagle Rock Trading Post. PayPal, Stripe, Squarespace, Google, and Eagle Rock Trading Post may collect personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site to complete purchase orders and track traffic to our site.Orders  If you purchase a product or service from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date).  We and our payment processors (i.e. PayPal and Stripe) use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.Tell-A-FriendIf you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s name and email address.  We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site.  Eagle Rock Trading Post stores this information for the sole purpose of sending this one-time email [and tracking the success of our referral program].  Your friend may contact us at eaglerocktrading@aol.com  to request that we remove this information from our database.Uses of Information   We only use the information you provide to us to complete your orders and send out our newsletter and specials. Google and Squarespace use your I.P. footprint to track  traffic and other analytics on the website. We do not share any personal information with any other third parties Communications from the SiteSpecial Offers and UpdatesWe will occasionally send you information on [products, services, special deals, promotions]  [You can sign up for these emails from us on our home page at the "Mailing List and/or Newsletter form" located on our home page.]Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option not to receive these types of communications.  Please see the “Choice and Opt-out.” NewslettersIf you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you.  Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe.  Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section. Service-related AnnouncementsWe will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so.  For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email.  Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.  If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account. [You may opt-out of these communications.  Please see “Choice and Opt-out.”] Customer ServiceBased upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcoming email to verify your orders.  We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes. Profile We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, [and/or third party sources] to create a “profile” of your preferences.  We tie your personally identifiable information, and [or] your purchasing history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you. We do not share your profile with other third parties.  Supplementation of Information In order to provide certain services [line of credit] to you, we may on occasion supplement the personal information you submitted to us with information from third party sources.           Credit CheckTo determine if you qualify for credit directly from Eagle Rock Trading Post, we will request additional information and use (your business name, your name, tax ID number, and/or social security number to request a credit report.  Once we determine your credit-worthiness, we destroy this document or keep it on file in your business/personal profile.            ID [Address] VerificationWe will use a third party to verify your [identity] [address], in order to determine a line of credit from us.   Personally identifiable information:   We DO NOT Share Personally Identifiable Information with Third Parties Agents     We use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.Service ProvidersWe use other third parties [PayPal and Stripe] to provide credit card payments on our site.  When you sign up for [PayPal service/membership] or complete the checkout order form, they will share [ verification, email address, and shipping address] as necessary for us to provide that service. {See our Payment and Privacy Page}.  These third parties are prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose.Other Third Parties  We use primarily USPS (United States Postal Service) for our shipping needs. On occassion we will use other shipper's (UPS, FedX, DHL, etc.) for large orders, overnite air, overseas air, and other specialty shipments. Legal DisclaimerWe reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web siteChoice/Opt-outWe provide you the opportunity to ‘opt-out’ of having your personally identifiable information used for certain purposes, when we ask for this information.  For example, if you purchase a product/service but do not wish to receive any additional marketing material from us, you can indicate your preference on our order form. Our promotional information will be listed on our facebook page. You can click on the Facebook logo at bottom of each page to visit our facebook page.If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at eaglerocktrading@aol.com  or you may contact us atEagle Rock Trading PostPO Box 311272New Braunfels, TX 78131  USAPh. 830-626-8309   Log FilesAs is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files.  This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.  We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.  We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.   CookiesA cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. Our payment service (PayPal) uses cookies to keep track of the item(s) you order on this site. [They do link the information they store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit to them while on our site.] We use [both] session ID cookies [and/or] persistent cookies.  [We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site.] A session ID cookie expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file. We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don’t have to enter it more than once.  Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site.  If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site will be limited. You will not be able to store multiple items in your shopping cart. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site.  We have no access to or control over these cookies. See “Third Party Advertisers.”This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Eagle Rock Trading Post only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. [See the “Third Party Advertisers” section.]  Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)We employ [or our third party advertising partner Vertical Response may employ] a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective.  Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users.  In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.To learn more about our advertising company’s use of clear gifs, please go to http://www.verticalresponse.com/We use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients.  This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.  If you would like to opt-out of these emails, please see “Choice and Opt-out.” You can request a text only newsletter also. Third Party AdvertisersAt this time we don't use any third party advertisers. If we do use them in the future The ads appearing on this Web site would be from a third party source.  Such advertisers would be Google Ad Words or Amazon Ads linking to websites with same or similar products to offer. If we were to use such advertising We would share Web site usage information about users with a reputable third party  for the purpose of targeting our Internet banner advertisements on this site. through this technology, your information is not personally identifiable.   Links to Other SitesThis Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Eagle Rock Trading Post. Please be aware that we, Eagle Rock Trading Post, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.  We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site.   Access to Personally Identifiable InformationIf your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may [correct, update, delete or deactivate it] by emailing our Customer Support at eaglerocktrading@aol.com  or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.Eagle Rock Trading PostPO Box 311272New Braunfels, TX 78131  USAPh: 830-626-8309 SecurityThe security of your personal information is important to us. We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it.  No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however.  Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send an email to us at eaglerocktrading@aol.com Business TransitionsIn the event Eagle Rock Trading Post goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred.  You will be notified via [email] [prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days] of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.Changes in this Privacy StatementIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.  We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently.  If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.Contact Us If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at eaglerocktrading@aol.com or:Eagle Rock Trading PostPO Box 311272New Braunfels, TX 78131  USAPh: 830-626-8309
When subscribing to our Newsletter:  If you do not see a confirmation email from us after you sign up to our Newsletter,  please check your spam/junk mail. You will need to confirm your email address and double opt-in, in order to receive your promo code for the 10% off.
Subscribe to our Newsletter Here
* required
Email Address: *
GDPR Consent (Please check box if you're located in the EU and consent to receive our Newsletters
First Name:
Last Name:
Email & Social Media Marketing by VerticalResponse
The shopping cart will give you the choice of paying with credit card when asked for payment information.   Click here  to read the details concerning returns.*SHIPPING-HANDLING*SERVICES OFFERED*fAQ*SIZING CHART*CURRENCY CONVERTER*PRIVACY POLICY*RESOURCES
Copyright 2002-2020 EAGLE ROCK TRADING POST All Rights Reserved
